import movieNames from '../data/movieNames.json';

export default [
  {
    question: 'Do You know what movie is this music from?',
    a: 'Frozen',
    b: movieNames[0],
    c: movieNames[1],
    d: movieNames[2],
    correct: 'a',
    soundSource: '/assets/sounds/frozen.mp3',
  },
  {
    question: 'Do You know what movie is this music from?',
    a: movieNames[3],
    b: movieNames[4],
    c: 'Batman',
    d: movieNames[5],
    correct: 'c',
    soundSource: '/assets/sounds/batman1989.mp3',
  },
  {
    question: 'Do You know what movie is this music from?',
    a: movieNames[6],
    b: 'Turning Forty',
    c: movieNames[7],
    d: movieNames[8],
    correct: 'b',
    soundSource: '/assets/sounds/czterdziestolatek.mp3',
  },
  {
    question: 'Do You know what movie is this music from?',
    a: movieNames[9],
    b: 'Edward Scissorhands',
    c: movieNames[10],
    d: movieNames[11],
    correct: 'b',
    soundSource: '/assets/sounds/edwardScissorhands.mp3',
  },
  {
    question: 'Do You know what movie is this music from?',
    a: movieNames[12],
    b: movieNames[13],
    c: movieNames[14],
    d: 'Hannibal',
    correct: 'd',
    soundSource: '/assets/sounds/hannibal.mp3',
  },
  {
    question: 'Do You know what movie is this music from?',
    a: 'Home Alone',
    b: movieNames[15],
    c: movieNames[16],
    d: movieNames[17],
    correct: 'a',
    soundSource: '/assets/sounds/homeAlone.mp3',
  },
  {
    question: 'Do You know what movie is this music from?',
    a: "The Queen's Gambit",
    b: movieNames[18],
    c: movieNames[19],
    d: movieNames[20],
    correct: 'a',
    soundSource: '/assets/sounds/queensGambit.mp3',
  },
  {
    question: 'Do You know what movie is this music from?',
    a: movieNames[21],
    b: movieNames[22],
    c: movieNames[23],
    d: 'The Mission',
    correct: 'd',
    soundSource: '/assets/sounds/mission.mp3',
  },
  {
    question: 'Do You know what movie is this music from?',
    a: movieNames[24],
    b: movieNames[25],
    c: movieNames[26],
    d: 'Master Thaddeus: The Last Foray in Lithuania',
    correct: 'd',
    soundSource: '/assets/sounds/panTadeusz.mp3',
  },
  {
    question: 'Do You know what movie is this music from?',
    a: movieNames[27],
    b: movieNames[28],
    c: 'Our Folks',
    d: movieNames[29],
    correct: 'c',
    soundSource: '/assets/sounds/samiSwoi.mp3',
  },
];
